Michael Goodman

Greater Nashville Area, TN

Phone: (731) 412-8301 | Email | LinkedIn | GitHub

Introduction

With an inquiring mind and a love for learning, I strive for success in anything I set my sights towards to find and share intriguing information in today's ever-changing field of relevant data. I hope to expand my experience and skillset so I may improve the daily lives of those which I am involved.

Primary Skills and Technologies

- Excel Spreadsheets
- SQL(Postgres)
 - pgAdmin4
- PowerBI Dashboards
- Tableau Visualizations
- SQL Alchemy
- Git/GitHub
- Anaconda
 - Jupyter Notebooks

- Python3
 - Pandas/ GeoPandas
 - Matplotlib/Pyplot
 - Folium
 - Seaborn
 - Beautiful Soup

Professional Experience

Nashville Software School

Nashville, TN

Nashville, TN

October 2020 - Present

January 2020 – October 2020

August 2018 – January 2020

July 2021 - January 2022

Analytics Apprenticeship Certification Course Projects

ytics Apprenticeship Certification Course Projec

- <u>Capstone placeholder</u>
- PowerBI Dashboard
- Tableu Dashboard
- Nashville Parks Geospatial Project

TriStar Centennial Medical Center

Nursing Unit Clerk/Secretary

Patient Transport Shift Supervisor

Patient Transporter

- Operation of multiple data systems
- Department purchase and resupply
- Team member hiring, training and guideline document creation
- Patient transportation
- Disease disinfection and department upkeep

Nissan North America

Smyrna, TN

January 2016 – July 2018 August 2014 – January 2016

Material Handler/Forklift Operator Mechanical Production Technician

- Supply transportation and distribution
- Power tool and heavy machine operations
- Vehicle part build and assembly

Education and Training

Nashville Software School

Nashville, TN

Data Analytics Apprenticeship

July 2021 - January 2022

Volunteer State Community College

Gallatin, TN

Varying courses completed

August 2020